[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":105703,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":178682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":35673,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":214356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1270,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":215627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":4613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":220240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1113,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":221353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":227574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":978,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":228553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":232255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":944,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":233199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum i s 6 or b igger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":236125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":237013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":239454,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":956,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":240411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":245124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":877,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":246002,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to  perform  +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":248308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":877,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":249186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5 ","response_history":["5"],"rt":2036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":251222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":832,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":252055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":254620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":255508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":22791,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":278301,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarl y, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":62178,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":340480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":347185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":821,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":348007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an ele ment is  the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":350392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1080,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":351472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":353485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Co rrect! T he inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":708,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":354194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2035,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":356230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":753,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":356984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Remembe r, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":359133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":742,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":359875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":34042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":393918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":31668,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":425587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Bec ause of  this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":77298,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":502887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":506599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1023,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":507623,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1811,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":509434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":19057,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":528492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":533082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":4871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":537953,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":540721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1136,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":541857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yeah","response_history":["Yeah"],"rt":20464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":562321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":14861,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":577182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":580636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 =  10 and  10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":581851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":584742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"12","response_history":["12"],"rt":4117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":588860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":593551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Wh at is 5  +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":596082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3014,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":599097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because the sum is less than 9, I do not subtract 9.","response_history":["5, becauyse the ","5, becauyse the","5, becauyse th","5, becauyse t","5, becauyse ","5, becauyse","5, becauys","5, becauy","5, because the sum is less than 9, I do not subtract 9."],"rt":15738,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":614836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. The number is larger than 9, therefore I subtract 9 from 12.","response_history":["12","1","3, t","3, ","3,","3. The number is larger than 9, therefore I dub","3. The number is larger than 9, therefore I du","3. The number is larger than 9, therefore I d","3. The number is larger than 9, therefore I subtract 9 from 12."],"rt":19833,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":634670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because it is always the identity?","response_history":["0, because it a","0, because  it is a lqay","0, because it is alqa","0, because it is alq","0, because it is always the ider","0, because it is always the identity?"],"rt":15502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":650172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":9810,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":659983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":662435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're left with 0","response_history":["6, bevcause this makes 9, once you re","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you r","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subyr","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you suby","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'er le","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'er l","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'er ","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'er","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'e","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're keft ","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're keft","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're kef","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're ke","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're k","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're k","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're ","6, bevcau se this  makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'rele","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you'rel","6, bevcause this makes 9, once you subtract 9 you're left with 0"],"rt":20474,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":682910,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, I just don't think it is.","response_history":["No ","No","No, I just don't think it is."],"rt":11013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":693924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I do not think so, from what I worked out.","response_history":["I do not think so, from what I worked out."],"rt":8110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":702035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, I think 5 is because.","response_history":["Yes, I think 5 is because it l","Yes, I think 5 is because it ","Yes, I think 5 is because it","Yes, I think 5 is because i","Yes, I think 5 is because ","Yes, I think 5 is because."],"rt":9315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":711351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure.","response_history":["Yes, ","Yes,","Yes","Ye","Y","I am not sure."],"rt":19878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":731229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":4680,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":735910,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"Inverse 1 +n -n","response_history":["Inverse 1 +n -n"],"rt":25098,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":761008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how y ou got y our answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"Inverse = x-n","response_history":["I do o","I do not know.","Inverse = x-n"],"rt":18112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":779121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure.","response_history":["I am not sure."],"rt":5984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":785106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4971,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":790078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":792340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":797414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corre t.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I'm not sure, it just seems right to me.","response_history":["I'm not sure, it just seems right to me."],"rt":9472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":806886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9629,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":816516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"From what I learned, I think this is right.","response_history":["From what I learned, I think this is right."],"rt":8583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":825100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":7897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":832997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":877,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":833875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"27","response_history":["27"],"rt":2329,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":836204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":838274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"High School","response_history":["High School"],"rt":4105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":842380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2373,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":844754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":1969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":846723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":848838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":850896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you  enjoy t his HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1788,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":852685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":854789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3139,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":857928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"D id you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":861202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":863418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]